MOHAMMAD JABIR

Noida, U.P 201301 = +917017429568 = mohd.jabir5157@gmail.com =

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Dedicated **Senior SEO Executive (GP Outreach Expert)** professional with a history of meeting company goals utilizing consistent and organized practices. Skilled in working under pressure and adapting to new situations and challenges to best enhance the organizational brand.

SKILLS

- Website Error Report
- SEO Keyword research
- Competitor analysis
- Technical SEO
- Local SEO
- SEMrush Error Report

- Backlink Audit
- SEO web content analysis
- Excel Skills Related SEO
- TOOL USING
- Ahref, Semrush, Screaming Frog, Flikover, Rank watch, Pure VPN, SEO Quake.
 Google Analytics, Google Search Console, Google Spreadsheets.

WORK HISTORY

SENIOR SEO EXECUTIVE (GP OUTREACH EXPERT) 02/2021 to Current **WEB SOLUTIONS PVT LTD**, Noida, India

- I Perform On Page Optimization in terms of website design, Content optimization, Keyword density, duplicate content, URL Structure, Keyword Research, Internal Link structure, Meta tags, Header tags, Alt tags, Sitemaps, Traffic tracking codes, Google Search Console, Google Tag Manager, Rel- canonical, Google Analytical Tool,
- I Creating Level 1 Website Audit Reports
- I Creating Technical SEO Suggestion Reports, Redirection, Broken Link, 404 Pages, Sitemaps, Robots tag, Page speed, etc.
- I Weekly Google Analytics Report
- I WYTLABS e-commerce the Agency Reports
- I Creating Monthly Performance Report
- I Ranking Updates & Backlinks Audit
- Provided detailed reporting and analyses on client website demographics and statistics using Google Analytics.
- I Proficient in Off Page Optimization for improving SERP positions for Client projects. Business Listing Submission, Directory Submission, Bookmarking, Profile linking, Article submission, Blog Submission, Outreach Guest Posting PPT & PDF submission Info graphic.

SEO EXECUTIVE 09/2019 to 01/2021

Pentarch Initiative Pvt Ltd , New Delhi, India

- Gained extensive knowledge in data entry, analysis and reporting.
- Skilled at working independently and collaboratively in a team environment.
- Developed and maintained courteous and effective working relationships.

SEO INTERN 10/2018 to 09/2019 **Worked Seoczar Pvt. Ltd**, Noida, India

- Assisted with day-to-day operations, working efficiently and productively with all team members.
- Developed strong communication and organizational skills through working on group projects.
- Provided professional services and support in a dynamic work environment.
- Analyzed SEO outreach goals and presented findings to marketing director.

EDUCATION

BCA: Bachelor of Computer Applications, **07/2018**

TMU Moradabad - Uttar Pradesh

12th: 2012

Uttarakhand Board

10th: 2009

Uttarakhand Board